♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
TV ANNOUNCER: And now,
Quahog Channel Five presents:
"Movie and a Bath
with a Guy Named Lou."
Hey. It's Saturday night,
and you know what that means.
We're gonna take a bath
and watch the 1984
interesting movie, Gremlins.
Now, the Gremlins are funny.
I don't know
if those things are puppets
or they put costumes
on dogs or something,
but let's press "play"
and find out, huh?
You can't get them things
wet, by the way,
but don't worry,
this don't affect that.
We interrupt this
program for some
breaking news,
which is why
I'm still
chewing a bagel.
Mmm.
Just-just roll
the footage.
JOYCE: A major drug bust
in Quahog today
as police seized
over 100 kilos of cocaine.
TUCKER (smacks lips):
Okay, I'm done.
That's right, Joyce.
Apparently,
there were 100 kilos of cocaine
right here in Quahog,
and yet my guy can't get dick.
JOYCE: Singled out
for special recognition
in orchestrating
today's drug bust
was Officer Joe Swanson.
It feels good to know that,
thanks to me and my colleagues,
a lot fewer people
will be injecting cocaine
into their penises tonight.
Is that a thing?
It's a great thing.
(small applause)
Great job, Joe!
Way to go!
There he is!
Hey, thanks, everybody.
Hey, guys.
Hey, Joe, I saw you on TV.
Now I have to go
through the five stages
of having a celebrity friend.
Oh, you're on TV!
That's so cool!
We're going right
to the top together.
Oh, you think
you're better than us, huh?
Just one (bleep)
stroke of luck,
and you're there
and I'm here.
I'm sorry I overreacted.
Look, you got to be careful.
You need someone looking out
for you, who knows you.
Someone you can trust.
Give me some money!
Man, that was some pretty
impressive police work, Joe.
Thanks, Quagmire.
I'll be honest,
it was nice to be acknowledged
by the chief for once.
Usually, he's just
reminding me
that whatever punk
I'm roughing up ain't worth it.
You son of a bitch!
I ought to kill you right here!
Hey! This punk's
not worth it.
You're right.
You're not worth it.
So, listen, if you guys
aren't doing anything later,
the chief's throwing me a little
party to celebrate my bust.
I am going to let Quagmire
answer first.
Yeah, I'll go.
I shall go, too.
Oh, great. I'll see
you guys tonight.
(tires screech)
Oh, God, buddy, I'm sorry.
You okay?
You bastard!
Well, now I've seen
Woodrow Wilson naked.
(grunts)
(yells)
(screaming)
(tires screech)
(whirring)
(electrical buzzing)
(steam hissing)
(whooshing)
(electrical buzzing)
(grunts)
(screaming cluck)
(whirring)
(screams)
(screaming cluck)
(whooshing)
(dramatic music plays)
Hey, Bonnie, I made a
major drug bust today.
The biggest one the
force has ever seen.
That's great, Joe.
You don't seem
very excited.
I mean, this is a
huge deal for me.
The chief is even throwing
me a party tonight.
I don't know
if I can take another
evening of
sympathetic eye contact
from all
the other wives.
Well, just so you know,
this is a really big deal.
They even asked me to be a guest
on  Muy Importante!
(Latin music plays)
ANNOUNCER:
Muy Importante!
ALL:
A donkey just bit
a child in the hallway.
Wow, I've never been
to a cop bar before.
Yeah, look at
the bartender.
I bet working here,
she's one of those women
who's tough as nails
and good at giving sass.
What will it be, fellas?
I'd like to cram both your boobs
into a martini glass.
(sobbing)
I-I think she's just
a normal woman.
To Joe Swanson!
And the biggest
drug bust
in the history
of Quahog!
(all cheering)
Officer Swanson, I just wanted
to say congratulations.
I'm Nora. I just joined the
force.
Nice to meet you.
Wow, I've heard
so much about you.
You're like a legend
at the academy.
Is it true you
got straight A's
in Officer Henderson's
Overintensity Workshop?
You're damn right I did!
Well, you did some
great work today.
And I mean
regular-person great,
not just
wheelchair-person great.
Yeah, I guess.
You seem a little distracted.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, sorry,
I was just thinking about...
someone should have come
tonight, but they didn't.
Ah, it's nothing.
That's good.
Hey, Officer Swanson?
Yeah?
You know how they say
never meet your heroes?
Well, they don't say anything
about kissing them.
Whoa!
Geez, every cop
in town is here.
I know. Who do you think is
taking care of the city?
No.
(horn honking)
MAN: What the hell?
Come on!
No drive. Is wet.
Hey-hey, fun party
last night, Joe.
You guys, I got something
to tell you.
The weirdest thing happened
to me at that party.
I got kissed
by this chick cop.
No way! What's she look like?
Is she hot?
Well, I don't know. Uh...
Is Elizabeth Perkins hot?
I... I, uh...
I-I don't... I don't know.
Way to go, Joe.
Did you bang her?
What? Of course
not, Quagmire.
I mean, I'm a
married man.
I could never
cheat on Bonnie.
Well, under normal
circumstances,
you'd be right
to say that,
but in this case,
cheating would be
the only fair thing.
What? What are you
talking about?
Come on. Didn't Bonnie
have that affair in Paris?
Oh, yeah. I don't want
to talk about that.
Joe, how can I put this
delicately?
He used his stinky French wiener
to defile her.
Wow. That's a...
real hit above the belt.
But I'm still not sure that's
a reason to betray Bonnie.
Come on, Joe. Sleeping with
this girl wi even things up.
You can't have that kind of
imbalance in your relationship.
In fact, you owe it to Bonnie
to have sex with this woman.
It's for the good
of your marriage.
Yeah, you should
go for it, Joe.
Secrets are what
keep a marriage fresh.
I have a CB radio
in the basement.
I go down there a couple times
a week to have CB sex.
Lois has no idea.
Breaker breaker one-nine.
What's your 20?
(woman speaks
in garbled, staticky voice)
Ah, it's so hot
just knowing you're in a truck.
Good morning,
Officer Swanson.
Oh, hey... Nora.
Uh, listen, I...
It's okay, Joe.
You don't need
to explain.
I stepped over the line
at the bar last night.
I'm... I'm sorry.
It's not that I don't
find you attractive.
I do. I just...
I'm married and...
I get it.
I totally
understand, Joe.
(phone ringing)
Excuse me.
Hello?
BONNIE:
Joe?
Bonnie?
Oh.
I-I meant to call someone else.
Yeah.
So, how is everything?
(click)
(sighs)
QUAGMIRE: Didn't Bonnie
have that affair in Paris?
PETER: He used his stinky
French wiener to defile her.
QUAGMIRE: Didn't Bonnie
have that affair in Paris?
PETER: He used his stinky
French wiener to defile her.
Hey, Quagmire,
we're in Joe's head.
Hey, let's mess with him.
I'm going to leave a fart
trapped in here.
(passing gas)
(Peter and Quagmire laughing)
PETER: All right,
let's get out of here.
(rapid footsteps,
car door opens and closes)
I want you.
I want you, too.
Come on.
I have a little
place we can go to.
NORA: Wow. I've
never seen a sofa
in a bathroom
stall before.
JOE: Well, I'm the only
one who comes in here,
so I figured I'd
make it my own.
How are you enjoying
your steak?
Mmm. It's delicious.
Let me put another
log on the fire.
(flame whooshing and crackling)
Thanks, Joe.
It was getting
a little chilly in here.
That's 'cause you're
all the way over there.
Well, let me
fix that.
(kissing)
Oh, Joe.
Oh, Nora.
Did you bring
protection?
Oh, don't worry.
Nothing comes out
of the front.
What a great day
for Joe and Bonnie.
This is Kevin's
first birthday
since he came home
from Iraq.
Why does Kevin always sit
at the bus stop,
but never gets on a bus?
Please don't
bring that up.
Don't bring
anything he does up.
Hey, you guys.
You're right on time.
Kevin just woke up screaming
from his afternoon nap.
Mom, it's my
birthday,
and you invited
your friends.
All yours are dead!
Hey, guys.
Uh, can I talk to
you for a second?
I did something
terrible.
Ah, hey, we've all
done terrible things.
Attention, everyone.
The plane is sinking,
so I need you all
to proceed onto the
floating slide.
PETER:
Dear airplane people,
I owe you one floating slide.
And just so you know,
the guy stewardess
was angry gay, not happy gay.
What does it say?
Nothing.
Just instructions
and stuff.
Oh, my God. You actually
went through with it?
How was it?
I don't know, you guys.
I thought I would feel better
after I slept with Nora,
but I don't.
I just feel really guilty.
And I'm not mad
at Bonnie anymore;
I'm just mad at myself.
Guys, am I the only one
who thinks it's weird
talking about Joe
cheating on Bonnie
in front of their baby?
MAN'S VOICE:
I think we can all benefit
from a little strange
now and then.
I know I will.
Uh-oh.
The baby monitor.
Wha...?
You cheated on me?
I-I, uh...
You bastard!
Bonnie, please.
After all
I do for you,
this is how
you repay me?
Well, how do you think
I felt when I found out
you slept with that
French guy, huh?
I never slept
with Francois.
What? But Peter said...
Lois, didn't you say
that Bonnie slept with him?
No, Peter. I said
she wanted to.
Damn it, Peter!
Now, hold on.
In my defense,
it is my experience
that I am generally correct
about most things.
You know what,
it doesn't matter.
Bonnie's been driving me away
for some time now.
What? Driving you away?
Do you have any idea
how hard it is living with you?
They still have
one of those TVs
with the big, fat back.
Maybe we should
all leave.
No!
Everyone stays.
I want this to
be a disaster.
'Cause this has been
a long time coming.
You care about nothing
except yourself.
You son of a bitch.
I got a license to operate
a sex crane for you.
And I got earplugs so I
could put up with that
(imitating Bonnie):
horrible voice of yours.
I'm not an impressionist,
but you get the idea.
I perform purification rituals
on my body after we have sex.
I find it cleanses
the immeasurable sadness
of having lain with a wretch.
I want a divorce!
You got it!
Sorry. I opened
some of the gifts.
Does the Swanson divorce
mean that I
have to go live
with Grandma and Grandpa?
No, Chris, it does not.
That doesn't even
make any sense.
Peter, I can't believe
you would encourage Joe
to have an affair.
Look, Lois, it's
in the Bible.
What's in the Bible?
I-I don't know.
Doesn't that always
cover it somehow?
Peter, you blew up
their marriage.
This was
a huge mistake.
Well, we've all made mistakes.
Eh.
(Stewie screaming)
Why did the sign say
"not an exit"?
It should have just said
"gorilla door."
(screaming)
So, it's really
over, huh?
After all
these years?
I'm afraid so.
But let's be
honest, Peter.
Bonnie and I seem
to have grown apart.
Boy, I never would have seen
this day coming
when we first met.
"Africa" by Toto was playing.
♪ ♪
♪ I hear the drums
echoing tonight ♪
♪ But she hears only whispers ♪
♪ Of some quiet conversation ♪
♪ I stopped an old man
along the way ♪
♪ Hoping to find
some long forgotten words ♪
♪ Or ancient melodies ♪
♪ He turned to me as if to say ♪
♪ "Hurry, boy,
it's waiting there for you" ♪
♪ It's gonna take a lot
to drag me away from you ♪
♪ There's nothing that a hundred
men or more could ever do ♪
♪ I bless the rains
down in Africa ♪
♪ Gonna take some time
to do the things we never had ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh... ♪
Lois, I know
how to get
Joe and Bonnie
back together.
Joe just told me
how he and Bonnie met.
So I figure, all we got to do
is find a way
to recreate the magic
of that night.
Well, we better
do something soon,
'cause I just
talked to Bonnie
and she's already
on D-Date.
What the hell's D-Date?
Diarrhea Date.
It's filthy.
But she found someone,
and they're doing whatever
they do tomorrow.
What the hell's
wrong with people?
Thanks for inviting
me to lunch, Lois,
but why are we eating
at a strip club?
I know the waitress here
from water aerobics.
She said she'd
give us 20% off.
All units, all units.
We have a disturbance
at the Fuzzy Clam.
This is Officer Swanson.
What's the problem?
Well, one of the dancers
was dancing with a guy
and saying, "You're my favorite,
you're my favorite,"
but now she's dancing
with another guy.
That's not a crime.
Well, shouldn't it be?
I'll be right there.
(siren whooping)
("Africa" by Toto playing)
Boy, I haven't heard this
song in a long time.
Police! What's going on?
Bonnie?
Joe?
What are you
doing here?
I'm here with Lois.
What are you doing here?
I got a call.
Is that... is that
"Africa" by Toto?
Yeah.
That's our song.
It is.
♪ But she hears only whispers
of some quiet... ♪
Well, it seems like
things are fine here.
Listen, Bonnie,
I, uh...
I just want to
say I'm sorry.
I was a real ass,
and I miss you.
I'm sorry, too.
I know I haven't been
that easy to live with lately.
Okay.
Well, I'm going
to go now.
Joe, wait.
You want a lap dance, mister?
No. Sit down.
I'm giving you one.
♪ The wild dogs
cry out in the night ♪
♪ As they grow restless ♪
♪ Longing for
some solitary company ♪
Oh, Joe.
Oh, Bonnie.
♪ He turned to me
as if to say... ♪
Can you ever
forgive me?
It's going to take
some time, Joe.
Rest of your life okay?
♪ It's gonna take a lot
to drag me away from you ♪
♪ There's nothing that a hundred
men or more could ever do ♪
♪ I bless the rains
down in Africa... ♪
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru